<?xml version="1.0"?>
<member id="botisn" group="g_istlab g_ois g_sense" joined="2016">
	<givenname>Nikiforos</givenname>
	<surname>Botis</surname>
	<memb_title>Mr.</memb_title>
	<email>nmpotis@dmst.aueb.gr</email> 
	<web_site>https://www.linkedin.com/in/nikiforosbotis</web_site> 
	<office_phone>+30 210 8203466</office_phone>
	<mobile_phone>6983609581</mobile_phone>
	<!--fax></fax> -->
	<!-- <alumnus/>--><!-- Optional -->
	<office_address>Derigny 12, 7th floor</office_address>
	<postal_address>76 Patission str, 104 34, Athens, Greece</postal_address>
	<photo>../images/Botis.jpg</photo>
	<shortcv>
		<p>
		    <i>Nikiforos Botis</i> holds a Bachelor’s degree with distinction from the Department of Management Science and Technology of the 
		    Athens University of Economics and Business (AUEB).
		</p><p> 
		    At January 2016, Nikiforos was admitted at University College London (UCL), in the department of Management Science and Innovation as part of the Erasmus+ program, 
	            where he spent the 6th semester of his undergraduate studies. At March 2016, Nikiforos participated in the InnoJam++ @CeBIT 2016 co-organized by SAP and Volkswagen in Hanover, 
                    a 32-hour hands-on experience in the latest technologies that are utilized by SAP, following his excellence at the SAP ERP labs which took place in the university 
                    (scoring at the 2.5% of the class). 
		</p><p>	
                     In his last year at AUEB, he worked as a Research and Development intern in the Dutch consultancy company Software Improvement Group, under the supervision of 
                     Dr. Yiannis Kanellopoulos. During his internship, Nikiforos developed a new way to holistically depict an Information System, named <a href="https://fsdet.dmst.aueb.gr//wp-content/uploads/2017/05/14_FSDET_paper_11.pdf">Information System Canvas</a>. 
                </p><p>
		     Currently, he is a postgraduate student at Imperial College London, pursuing a Master’s degree at Computer Science. He has been awarded two scholarships 
		     (from the General Michael Arnaoutis Foundation and the Greek State Scholarship Foundation) in order to fund his studies. 
                     Nikiforos has joined the SENSE (currently <a href="https://www.balab.aueb.gr/nikiforos-botis.html">BA</a>) group in March 2016 and the OIS group in October 2016 as a research assistant.
		</p>
	</shortcv>
</member>
